<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">AndroidRally</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_refresh">Refresh</string>
    <string name="action_help">Help</string>
    <string name="current_games">Current games</string>
    <string name="title_activity_game_configuration">Set up</string>
    <string name="round_time">Round time</string>
    <string name="card_time">Card time</string>
    <string name="round_time_default">12 hours</string>
    <string name="card_time_default">45 seconds</string>
    <string name="players_text">Number of bots</string>
    <string name="number_of_players_default">4 bots</string>
    <string name="start_button">Start Game</string>
    <string name="set_up_button">Set up game</string>
    <string name="new_game">Start new game</string>
    <string name="start_game">Create game</string>
    <string name="help">Placeholder for help</string>
    <string name="close_help">Done</string>
    <string name="gamemode">Game mode</string>
    <string name="singleplayer">Single player (Local)</string>
    <string name="multiplayer">Single player (Server)</string>
    <string name="delete_game">Do you want to delete this game?</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="title_activity_help">Help</string>
    <string name="general_game_idea">The game is won by reaching all checkpoints before your opponents. This is done by selecting the right cards to program your robot to navigate through the map and other robots. Avoid taking damage and losing lives as you only got three lives to use.</string>
    <string name="round">In every round, each robot will receive up to nine cards, lowered by one per damage the robot has taken. You should select five of these when trying to guide the robot to the next checkpoint. (If damage taken is 5 or higher cards are beginning to be locked into the position they had the previous round). After all robots have performed a card the board elements on the map will execute their actions. Consider this when you choose your cards. The last thing to happen before the next card is executed is that all robots and stationary lasers will fire their laser straight forward and if they hit a robot it will take one damage.</string>
    <string name="board_elements">The gameboard contains various board elements which can affect your robot in both positive and negative ways.</string>
    <string name="checkpoints">The game is won by standing on all checkpoints in the correct order. Remember that the checkpoints are the last board elements executing its action so be careful not to be pushed away before all checkpoints are done. A checkpoint will also repair one damage from the robot if it is the robot’s next checkpoint.</string>
    <string name="conveyor_belt">This element will push you in the direction the arrows are pointing, the distance you will be pushed varies depending on how many arrows there are on a single tile.</string>
    <string name="gears">A gear will rotate you 90° in the direction the arrows are pointing.</string>
    <string name="repair">This will repair your robot reducing the damage taken by one.</string>
    <string name="hole">Do not walk into a hole! It will cause you to die which means that you lose a life and will not be able to move more that round. The same is true for walking out of the map.</string>
    <string name="dock">This will be the starting position for the robot with the specific number.</string>
    <string name="help_h1">General game idea</string>
    <string name="help_h2_board_element">Board elements</string>
    <string name="h_checkpoints">Checkpoints</string>
    <string name="h_picture_round">1. Displays how long time you got to choose your cards.\n2.  Displays how much damage the robot has taken. Also shows how many cards that are locked from previous round because of damage. When the robot has enough damage it will die.\n3. Displays how many lives the robot has left.\n4. The card which will be executed first when the round starts. You should fill all the five slots, otherwise the ones you left empty will be filled with random cards.\n5. Sends the cards to the game. You cannot change cards after sending them!</string>
    <string name="h_conveyor_belts">Conveyor belts</string>
    <string name="h_gears">Gears</string>
    <string name="h_repair">Repair</string>
    <string name="h_holes">Holes</string>
    <string name="h_dock">Dock</string>
    <string name="h_laser">Laser</string>
    <string name="laser">Lasers shoot at the same time as robots. They will add one damage token to your robot if a laser hits. You can be hit by multiple lasers at the same time and receive many damage tokens.</string>
    <string name="h_round">Round</string>

</resources>